Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide.
Raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary.
Till someone proves it real.
Through it all, through all the trouble.
At times through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are.
That was way off the mark.
Hey, what's so loud down there?
Cannon firing practice.
But it's not going very well.
Like I said, let the expert aim the thing.
Judging from the flying distance of
the last one, this should do it. Fire!
Awesome!
You hit that thing on the
first try! Wow, I did.
What you think I'm pretty magnificent when
it comes to aiming so
are you impressed yet?
Yeah, you better believe
it So it's all set.
You'll be our sniper.
I don't get to be captain.
No, I'm still the captain
Whatever I'll hear me you for now
But the second you do something cowardly.
I'm taking your post I can live with that
But you know guys I was
thinking there's one
other position that we
have to fill before we
can head out for the
Grand Line You're right.
The kitchen is really nice on this ship.
Just pay me and I'll do it.
I suppose it is vital for long trips.
No decent pirate ship
should be without one.
A musician.
Are you an idiot?
What do you think we're doing out here?
Just when I thought you were
gonna say something smart.
But we're pirates and pirates
sing a lot, didn't you know?
Get out here, you damn pirates!
Hey, what the hell?
Who are you? Shut up!
Who I am means nothing!
You stinking pirate!
Hey, guys.
How many are there?
Uh, one.
Then just let him handle it.
Over the years, I've lost count of
all the pirate heads we've taken.
And now you guys think
you can kill my partner?
That voice.
What do you mean by partner?
Look, I don't know what this is!
Just stop wrecking my ship!
What are you doing here Johnny, huh?
Who's saying my name like they
think they know me or something?
Go big bro Zoro Johnny.
It is you.
What are you doing here big bro?
Hey relax. Is everything okay?
Where's Yosaku?
Well
Hey, look, Zoro knows that guy.
What's going on here?
He's been sick.
What is it?
Up until a few days ago, he
was healthy and full of life.
And now, he keeps fainting
and getting really pale.
I have no idea what's causing it.
His teeth had been falling out and his
old wound opened up and started bleeding.
It just got worse and worse.
I didn't know what to do.
So I thought maybe we'd just
rest on a little island.
But then...
A cannonball came flying from this ship!
We're very sorry.
Sorry isn't good enough.
Isn't that right, partner?
Big bro, give it to me straight.
Is he gonna die?
He's so dumb.
Watch it.
Stop it.
Whatever you're doing, stop.
You're mocking his death.
Dammit, you'll die.
Luffy, Usopp, we have
some limes in storage.
What are you doing?
Bring them here, now.
No, you get out of the way!
Come on, move it.
He's got scurvy.
Scurvy? Mm-hmm.
If we weren't too late, he'll
be just fine in a few days.
Really, Big Sis? Really?
Thank you, Big Sis!
Please, don't call me that.
It sounds so dumb.
Besides, I'm not a magician.
This used to be a hopeless
disease that plagued sailors.
and we just know how to deal with it now.
Here, there you go.
Drink up, sick guy.
I have some more.
This is caused by a simple deficiency of
plant-derived nutrients, like vitamin C.
Back in the old days, they couldn't
carry fresh fruits and vegetables?
because they couldn't store them.
We know better now.
If a little is good, a lot is good.
You're gonna be just fine.
You're smart.
You're like a doctor.
Well, now, how about that?
I was right.
She isn't dumb.
You guys are morons!
Every sailor should know about scurvy!
It scared me! Hooray! You're all better!
You can't kill that quickly!
Allow us to introduce ourselves.
My name is Johnny.
And I'm Yosaku.
Together, we're the baddest pirate
bounty hunting duo in the world.
Big Bro Zoro there used to be one of us.
Glad to make your acquaintance.
Small world.
Never thought I'd see you guys again.
Well, if you think you're surprised.
We never imagined that the pirate
hunter Zoro became a pirate himself.
Tell me about it.
Big Bro.
Hey, partner!
Let this be a lesson to you.
Yeah, this is the kind of trouble you run
into when you choose a life on the sea.
Which means when we're at sea,
we really gotta think
about how we can get the
right amount of nutrients
with very little food.
It's absolutely necessary that someone
on the ship knows how to do that.
It's necessary.
Right, the ship needs a cook.
Let's go find us a cook.
I'm in?
Good idea.
We'll have yummy food even
while we're out at sea.
That's right, you got it.
A cook?
I know just the place, and the
food is going to blow your mind.
Consider yourselves warned.
This place is close to the Grand Line,
And I've heard a lot
of rumors lately that a
certain Hawkeye man you're
looking for is there!
Set a course North-North-East,
Awesome!,
Our destination is?
The sea restaurant, the Reverie!
So, what do you think?
Whoa, it's a big fish! How lovely!
This is the coolest place ever!
Just like I told you, right?
What the?
A marine ship?
All the way out here?
Hey, Luffy, they're not going
to start firing at us, are they?
But how did that ship...
I've never seen that pirate flag.
So, do you think he knows that you
and I aren't a couple of pirates?
Uh...
I am Iron Fist Fullbody.
But you can just call me sir.
You there! Who's the captain?
Identify yourself.
My name is Luffy.
My name is Usopp. Got it?
We only made our flag
the day before yesterday.
That's right, Marine.
And I drew it.
You did.
Is that so?
Hey, you two. Right there.
I've seen you before.
You're that bounty hunter duo that
goes after the small fish, right?
Yeah, well, we...
So, you've finally been caught by pirates.
Yeah, well, actually, we...
Now that's a laugh.
Hey, come on, baby, let's get going. Sure.
Hey, wait a minute!
You think small-type bounty
hunters would go after these guys?!
Now, let's go to that restaurant.
They're an eyesore.
Sink them. Sir!
He ignored us.
Next time we see him, he better
have a little more respect for us.
What are these things?
Well, those are all wanted
pirates, big sis not...
In other words, if we defeat
them, we get the reward money.
Pretty lucrative business, huh, big sis?
Hey, you guys, look!
They're pointing out cannon right at us!
Leave it to me!
Now, Gum-Gum!
Let's range on!
Sir!
Are you all right, Head Chef Zep?
Sir, are you okay?
Head Chef, are you sure you're okay?
No!
Nothing is okay!
Never mind!
Just get back to the restaurant already!
But, but sir, aren't you,
I mean... You maggots!
Do you want to see me angry?
Feeding the customer is a cook's job!
What are you trying to do?
Put me out of business?
This is the guy.
He's the one responsible for this.
Hmm?
Sir, I'm very sorry!
I see.
Good to know!
But I'm all banged up.
The medical fees and repair charges
for the ship are gonna cost you!
I
Won't ask you to cut me any slack.
Oh, but
I'M FLAT BROKE! Hm. Hm.
Well, you're pretty direct, huh?
If you don't have money,
you've no choice but to work. Fine!
I wanna make it right!
Then you'll work,
unpaid, for a whole year.
I'll let you off the hook with that.
A year?!
Did you just say a year?!
A whole year?!
What's taking Luffy so long? Yeah.
They'll probably make him work
without pay for like a whole month.
He should have just
said it was the Marine's
fault instead of being so freaking honest.
Oh, wow.
That guy sitting over there
is Lieutenant Full Body.
Well, what do you know?
Hey, look, kids.
A big shot from HQ.
Oh, wow.
He's so elegant.
You're famous.
Everybody in here is looking at you.
No, you're wrong.
They're all admiring you.
Hmm.
So good.
This flavor.
And yes, the aroma.
It is the unmistakable scent from
the soil of Mock of the Northland,
bitter with plenty of
body and just a tad sour.
This wine must be...
the famous Ituruts Burgerstein.
Tell me, waiter.
Am I right?
Uh-uh.
Not even close, sir.
Eat up.
This dish is best when hot.
And, sir, my name's
Sanji. I'm the Zeus chef.
All the waiters ran off as of yesterday.
You really should be fine.
I can't help it.
He looks so confident.
Do you know a lot?
About wine?
Yes, I thought.
But it seems my sense of
taste isn't working today.
What's going on?
I'm certain I requested
that the owner serve
that particular wine when
I made this reservation.
I can only work for one week.
Yeah, right.
A week, get real.
Fine, then. Two!
Hey, you wrecked my restaurant and
seriously injured the head chef.
That's a serious offense.
You can't just settle that up with
one or two weeks of unpaid work.
That's ridiculous you win three weeks
Talk to me?
No deal!
I waited ten long years
to become a pirate.
So, I'm not gonna waste another
year stuck in this restaurant!
Hmm?
Okay, listen.
I'm gonna get you to let
me off the hook in a week.
That's my decision. Hmm.
If you value your time so much,
I'll tell you what you can do
to settle your debt quickly,
you runt.
Oh!
It'll cost you...
a leg, my boy.
Oh, that's pricey.
Heh.
Good, I got your attention.
Waiter! Hey!
Get over here!
I believe I've already
told you I'm not a waiter.
What an irresistible beauty you are.
My lady, would you care to join
me elsewhere for a glass of wine?
Hey, what is this?
Is bug soup on the menu today, or did
you make it just for me? Bug soup?
That's right.
What's this bug doing there, waiter?
This is going to ruin the
restaurant's reputation.
Sorry, sir. Don't know, really.
Looks like he's floating.
Then again, it kind of looks like he's
drowning, but it's hard to say for sure.
Don't you mess with me!
Waiter!
You could have eaten it if you
had just taken the bug out.
It would have been wonderful.
It took three full days of hard
cooking to prepare that soup for you,
and you wasted it.
Can't you see that you're biting
off more than you can chew?
I'm the customer here!
Do you understand me?
I'm paying you!
Stop it! Full Body! Shut up!
No, Full Body, no.
Can your money truly satisfy your hunger?
What do you mean I'm asking
can it satisfy your hunger?
This is getting old you're never gonna
make it if you don't just give in!
Sometimes it's still no no respect.
Oh my it's it's Sanji
what's going on here?
Hmm, a fight.
Don't ever waste food around me again.
At sea, if you ever provoke your cook,
you're signing your own death warrant.
Remember that.
Just hold it.
Almost there.
Customer service equals love
and love equals restaurant.
The customer is the king.
Pleasant greetings to the
customer is what it's all about.
The customer is always right!
And we stand by that.
Hello and welcome.
You damn crooks!
But don't you ever come back?
I'm really sorry about that.
You're all so pathetic. I laugh.
Ah, yes, indeed.
Today will be a great day for everyone.
Oh, hello there and
welcome, you damn crook.
That's our service motto around here.
No doubt about it.
The customer is our...
Oh, no, our customer.
Damn it, not again, Sanji.
What do you think you're
doing to our customer?
Can't you see he's a marine lieutenant?
You're a terrible cook.
What makes you think that
you can talk to me like that?
A crappy cook like you is calling me bad?
Restaurants can't exist
without their customers.
They're our lifeblood, so we don't want to
hurt them the way you seem to keep doing.
But he deserved it.
He didn't treat the
food or me with respect.
And he insulted all the cooks.
So I simply taught him a lesson.
You're gonna regret this.
All of you, no restaurant should
treat its customers like this.
I'll shut you down.
Do you understand me?
I will shut you down!
This entire place!
This whole restaurant is
finished! Do you hear me?
Then, maybe I should
just finish you off now.
Arrogant assholes like you
who think they're such big
shots they can push anybody
around really piss me off!
You can't keep doing this in
the restaurant every other day!
You're not such a big
shot now, are ya? Are ya?
What happened?
Are they okay?
I can breathe again!
Boss Zef, what's happening here?
You didn't hurt yourself, did you?
Damn it!
My ceiling!
Another thing that's gonna have
to get fixed because of you!
This is all your fault, you brat!
How is it my fault?
You attacked me!
Boss, can you stop messing
around and give us a hand?
Sanji's gone crazy again!
Hey, Sanji!
Don't tell me you went on another
rampage in here, you idiot!
Put a cork in it, old man!
Oh, now you're ordering me around!
Just who do you think you're talking to?
Do you want to sink my restaurant
to the bottom of the sea?
You punk!
You two, get your ass
out of my restaurant!
What kind of restaurant is this?
That boss is like a gangster.
It's almost as if...
if this were a pirate ship.
How can you deny our customer is king?
The only kingly customers are the ones
who stomach the slop that you call food.
That's it.
If you two want to fight,
you'll keep it in the kitchen.
You understand me?
Are all these idiots really cooks?
Lieutenant!
Lieutenant Fullbody!
We've got trouble!
Wow, this restaurant is crazy.
Sir, he's escaped!
Pirate Creek's henchman
attacked us and vanished!
He what? Well, sir,
we've already lost seven of
our men and the only thing
we wanted out of him was
a lead on fighting Creek.
Impossible.
When we picked him up three days ago,
he was right on the verge
of starving to death.
And we haven't fed him anything.
Where did he get the strength?
Greek pirates.
They're the ones who are said to be
the fiercest pirates in the East Blue.
I'm sorry, Lieutenant, I'm...
Would seem we have a new customer, sir.
It do well to mind his manners and
not start any trouble on my ship.
A pirate, huh?
I don't care what it is.
Just bring me something to eat.
Come on, this is a restaurant.
Hello and welcome, you damn crook!
I'm just gonna say this one more time.
and bring me something
to eat and make it quick.
That cook is gonna get us killed.
Of course, right away,
but might I be so bold to inquire
how you're paying for your meal?
Will a bullet be enough?
So you don't have any money then?
That dumbass Patty broke into the chair.
Whoa, what power.
Sorry, pirate, but our policy is
to only serve paying customers.
Kick his ass, Paddy! Show that, pirate!
We cooks don't screw around!
Oh, I can hear your stomach
grumbling from here, pirate.
That was a fart, jerk.
Now listen, get me something to eat now.
We're not getting you
anything, so beat it!
I can't take it anymore.
All of these cooks are insane.
I've got to get out of here.
I don't want anything to do
with this place ever again.
Kick him! Come on!
And now, you damn crooks!
If you need anything, just ask, okay?
And please, never come back!
Dammit!
If I wasn't so weak from
hunger, I'd be inside eating.
How beautiful and cruel this ocean can be.
It's almost a death sentence to
lose your food and water out here.
How difficult it is to survive.
I know what it means to go hungry
because of the sea more than anyone.
You can die for your pride if you want.
But listen, if you eat and survive,
won't that give you the
opportunity to fight for
pride truly worth having
now and in the future?
I'm sorry.
Thank you so much.
I thought it was over.
I truly thought I was going to die.
This fruit, it's delicious.
I've never eaten food this good before.
Of course it is.
I think I just found my cook.
You're lucky he gave you some food.
You weren't looking so good there.
I thought you were a goner. So listen, Mr.
Cook, why don't you leave
this boat and join my crew?
I could use a cook like
you on my pirate ship.
Huh? Huh?
That I knew would lead me.
I had to find my way to that place.
Before someone could beat me!
The promised land was in my grasp.
And I wouldn't let go.
La la la la la?
My only dream.
I won't stop chasing
it until it comes true.
But if the world ever
changes, I call out your name.
We can return to the time
when everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade.
Waiting for that one true dream?